Kyle Goetke

101 Overhill Rd, Summit, NJ 07901 cell (908) 499-8047 goetkek@gmail.com

Profile

Motivated high school student with background knowledge in IT services and computer hardware, leadership experience, and strong problem-solving and interpersonal skills. Experience working with enterprise-level hardware in a professional environment.

Technical Skills

Languages: Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL

Certifications: IC3 Digital Literacy, Microsoft Office Specialist, CompTIA IT

Fundamentals, Oracle Database Foundations

Additional Experience: Windows, Ubuntu Linux, Building Computers, Team Programming, Pair

Programming, Database Management

Education

Union County Academy for Information Technology

2016 - Present, will graduate in 2020

- Completed AP Computer Science Principles and AP Computer Science A
- Served as a club officer and Chair of the Hardware Committee for the AIT Coding Club
- Served as Class Historian
- Academic Honor Roll: 2016 2018
- Completed Web Design and Cybersecurity courses

Work Experience

Union County Vocational-Technical Schools / IT Intern

2019 - Present

- Assisted school faculty with technology issues
- Responsible for organizing and setting up new hardware for incoming students
- Responsible for maintaining existing technology

New Providence School District / Technology Assistant

Summers of 2016, 2017, & 2018

- Responsible for sorting and installing new hardware and software.
- Assisted with organizing old hardware and software.
- Cooperated with team members to integrate new and old technology.

Other Experience

Appalachia Service Project / Volunteer

Summers of 2017 & 2019

Helped repair homes and improve living conditions for low-income families.

Boy Scouts of America / Life Scout

2013 - Present

- Held several positions of responsibility including Senior Patrol Leader and Junior Assistant Scoutmaster.
- Working towards achieving Eagle Scout.

Personal Projects

Python Programs

- Created multiple programs to assist with schoolwork
 - Molar mass calculator for Chemistry
 - Kinematic equation solver for Physics

Linux Bash Scripts

- Created scripts to automate tasks
 - Enabling low-power mode for a laptop
 - Updating the system and programs
 - Displaying system information